(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-09-05T22:20:12.082995",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
あ！
Ah!
おはよう！
Good morning!
私、今来たところ。
I just got here myself.
全然待ってないよ。
I haven't been waiting long at all.
むしろ、今日は来てくれてありがとう！
If anything, thanks for coming today!
いい天気だね。
It's lovely weather, isn't it?
私さ、
You know,
ずっと君とこうやって公園とか散歩したいと思ってたんだ。
I've always wanted to take a walk in the park with you like this.
あのさ...
Hey...
手...繋いでもいいかな？
Can we... hold hands?
やったー！
Yay!
繋ごう！
Let's hold hands!
手を繋いでると、なんかドキドキするね。
Holding hands makes my heart beat faster.
いよいよこれから生誕ライブか...
The birthday live is finally starting soon...
緊張するな...
I'm so nervous...
君ももちろん来てくれるよね？
You're coming too, of course, right?
ありがとう！
Thank you!
今日のために歌とかダンスとか、いっぱい練習してきたから...
I've practiced singing and dancing so much for today...
絶対見てほしいと思ってたんだ。
...so I really wanted you to see it.
絶対見つけるね！
I'll definitely spot you in the crowd!
あ、あそこにベンチがあるよ。
Ah, there's a bench over there!
ちょっと座って話そう？
Shall we sit down and talk for a bit?
なんかさ、一つの椅子に隣同士で座るとさ...
You know, sitting side-by-side on the same bench...
なんか...ドキドキするね。
...it kind of makes my heart flutter.
ふふっ、可愛い。
Hehe, so cute.
ところで、お昼ご飯食べた？
By the way, have you eaten lunch yet?
そっか...まだ食べてないんだ。
I see... so you haven't eaten yet.
そうだと思って
Thinking that might be the case,
実は今日
actually, today...
君のために手作りのお弁当作ってきたんだ
I made a handmade bento for you!
一緒に食べよう
Let's eat together!
ありがとう
Thank you.
じゃっじゃーん
Ta-da!
見て
Look!
これお弁当箱可愛いでしょ
Isn't this bento box cute?
中身何入ってると思う？
What do you think is inside?
卵焼き？
Rolled omelet?
から揚げ？
Fried chicken?
ハンバーグ？
Hamburger steak?
うんうん、なるほど
Mm-hmm, I see.
正解はこちらでしたー！
The correct answer is this!
わあ、美味しそう
Wow, it looks delicious!
どうかな？AZKiの手作りお弁当
How is it? AZKi's handmade bento!
題して「あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー弁当」だよ
Titled: "Zero Guesser for Your Heart Bento"!
君の好きな卵焼きもちゃんと入ってます
It includes your favorite rolled omelet too!
正解だよ
So you were right!
それじゃあ何から食べる？
Well then, what will you eat first?
ソーセージ？
Sausage?
トマト？
Tomato?
卵焼き？
Rolled omelet?
うんうん
Mm-hmm...
やっぱり大好物の卵焼きからかー
Starting with your favorite rolled omelet after all?
本当好きだよね
You really love it, don't you?
じゃあ、さあ
Then, here...
あーんしてあげようか？
Shall I feed you? Say "Ah"!
もう、うなずきすぎだよ、可愛いな
Geez, you're nodding so much. So cute.
はい、じゃあ、あーん
Here, go "Ah"...
どう？美味しい？
How is it? Is it tasty?
ありがとう、嬉しい
Thank you! I'm so happy.
はい、じゃあもう一口、あーん
Alright, one more bite! Say "Ah"...
美味しそうに食べるね、作った甲斐があった
You look like you're really enjoying it! It was worth making.
美味しそうに食べてる君も、AZKiは好きだよ
AZKi loves seeing you eat so happily too!
食べてる君の姿見てたら、AZKiも元気出た
Seeing you eat gave AZKi lots of energy!
今日の生誕ライブも頑張れそうだよ
I feel like I can give my best at today's birthday live!
それじゃあ、そろそろリハーサルの時間だから、行ってくるね
Well then, it's almost time for rehearsal, so I'm gonna go!
絶対見つけるからね
I'll definitely find you in the crowd!
ライブが終わったら、また待ち合わせね
Let's meet up again after the live concert, okay?
せーの！
One, two!
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's a no-no
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, that's already
心は進化するよ
Getting our hearts moving on
もっと もっと
Further and further
言葉にすれば消えちゃう関係なら
If the bond is gone soon as it's put to words,
言葉を消せばいいやって
Better not say anything,
思ってた 恐れてた
Or so I thought, backing away,
だけど あれ？ なんかちがうかも..
But eh? Something's wrong with that...
せんりのみちもいっぽから！
Every long journey begins with one little step!
石のようにかたい そんな意志で
With a stern determination that is set in stone,
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ？
Build a pile of garbage up to become Yamato Nadeshiko?
「し」抜きで いや 死ぬ気で！
Disregard the "shi"? Nope, disregard my life!
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffily, fluffity,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
When you call my name,
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
Just that will make me go floating in the air.
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Fluffity, fluffily,
あなたが笑っている
When you show your smile,
それだけで 笑顔になる
Just that will make me smile.
神様 ありがとう
Dear God, thank you.
運命のいたずらでも
Even if it's just destiny pulling a prank on me,
めぐり逢えたことが
I'm so glad of the fact that
しあわせなの
We both had met.
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's a no-no
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
See, that's already
心は進化するよ
Getting our hearts moving on
もっと もっと
Further and further
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yup, that's a no-go
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
Hey, that's a bit too early
私のこと 見ててね
Don't take your eyes off me
ずっと ずっと
Never and ever
私の中のあなたほど あなたの 中の私の存在は
The more of you in me, and that my existence in you,
まだまだ 大きくないことも わかってるけれど
I know that I'm not as big as you,
今この同じ 瞬間
But I know, in this same moment,
共有してる 実感
I feel that we share the same moment.
ちりもつもればやまとなでしこ！
If all the dust settles, I'll be a Yamato Nadeshiko!
略して？ちりつもやまとなでこ！
For short? If the dust settles, it's Yamato Nadeko!
くらくらり くらくらる
Dizzily, dizzying,
あなたを見上げたら
When I look up at you,
それだけで まぶしすぎて
Just that will make me dazzled by your radiance.
くらくらる くらくらり
Dizzying, dizzily,
あなたを想っている
Just thinking of you,
それだけで とけてしまう
is enough to make me melt away.
神様 ありがとう
Dear God, thank you so much.
運命の いたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate,
めぐり逢えたことが
I am so happy that
しあわせなの
we were able to meet.
コイスル キセツハ ヨクバリ circulation
The season in love is a greedy circulation.
コイスル キモチハ ヨクバリ circulation
The feeling of love is a greedy circulation.
コイスル ヒトミハ ヨクバリ circulation
The eyes in love are a greedy circulation.
コイスル オトメハ ヨクバリ circulation
The maiden in love is a greedy circulation.
ふわふわり ふわふわる
Fluffily, fluffing around,
あなたが名前を呼ぶ
when you call my name,
それだけで 宙へ浮かぶ
just that makes me float into the air.
ふわふわる ふわふわり
Fluffing around, fluffily,
あなたが笑っている
when you are smiling,
それだけで 笑顔になる
just that brings a smile to my face.
神様 ありがとう
Dear God, thank you so much.
運命の いたずらでも
Even if it's a prank of fate,
めぐり逢えたことが
I am so happy that
しあわせなの
we were able to meet.
でも そんなんじゃ だめ
But that's a no-no,
もう そんなんじゃ ほら
see, if it stays like that, look,
心は進化するよ
my heart will evolve
もっと もっと
more and more!
そう そんなんじゃ やだ
Yeah, I don't want it like that,
ねぇ そんなんじゃ まだ
hey, if it stays like that, not yet...
私のこと 見ててね
keep your eyes on me,
ずっと ずっと
forever and ever!
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that!
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to try a single bite.
恋人みたいなことしてみたいの
I want to try doing lover-like things,
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to eat one bite.
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that!
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to try a single bite.
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...is what I couldn't bring myself to say today.
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
"I just want to eat one bite!"
目が合うだけで頬が緩む
Just meeting your eyes makes my cheeks soften,
目尻のしわくちゃ たまらないの
the crinkles at your eyes are irresistible!
週末 弾けた恋模様
On the weekend, a blooming romance pattern...
心が微熱どころではない
My heart is way beyond a slight fever.
ときめきの夢に酔いしれて
Drunk on a dream of fluttering excitement,
いっそこそのまま死んでもいい…？！
I wouldn't mind dying right like this...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, it's because I love you!
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stand still.
幸せを噛み締めていたいな
I want to savor this happiness.
ずっとこのまま 覚めないで
Forever like this, don't wake me up,
あともう一口だけ
just one more bite.
許されるならば夢を見せて
If it's permitted, let me dream on.
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that!
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to try a single bite.
間接キスなんてもう気にしないよ
I don't even care about indirect kisses anymore,
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to eat one bite!
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that!
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to try a single bite.
……あなたが好きすぎて言い出せないよ
...I love you too much to say it out loud!
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
"I just want to eat one bite!"
もうそろそろ気持ちが爆発しそうだよ
Any moment now, my feelings are gonna explode!
抱きしめてみたいよ
I want to try hugging you,
……でも引かれたら立ち直れないし。。
...but if you get turned off, I won't recover...
臆病なの、変わらないや
I'm just a coward, nothing changes.
目が合うだけで心臓が飛ぶ
Just meeting your eyes makes my heart leap!
せめて手だけは繋ぎたいの
At least, I want to hold your hand!
週末 弾けた恋模様
On the weekend, a blooming romance pattern...
心が微熱どころではない
My heart is way beyond a slight fever.
もう一度 夢に酔いしれて
Drunk on a dream once again,
連れ出して！
take me away!
いっそこそのまま死んでもいい…？！
I wouldn't mind dying right like this...?!
大袈裟じゃないよ 好きだから
I'm not exaggerating, it's because I love you!
時間が止まってしまったらいいのにな
I wish time would just stand still.
幸せを噛み締めていたいな
I want to savor this happiness.
ずっとこのまま 覚めないで
Forever like this, don't wake me up,
あともう一口だけ
just one more bite.
許されるならば夢を見せて
If it's permitted, let me dream on.
日が暮れるまで傍に居て
Stay by my side until the sun sets,
初キスはもう少し後で
our first kiss can wait a little longer.
束縛は強めでOK？
Is a bit of heavy possessiveness okay?
受け止めて 受け止めて
Accept me, accept me!
何も言わずに手を引いて
Take my hand without saying a word,
そのまま遠くへ連れてって
and take me far away just like that.
どこまでも どこまでも
Anywhere and everywhere...
ねぇ、それ一口ちょうだいよ
Hey, give me a bite of that!
一口だけ食べたいの
I just want to try a single bite.
……とは言い出せなかった今日のデート
...is what I couldn't bring myself to say today.
"...is what I couldn't say on our date today."
ヒトクチダケ、タベタイノ
"I just want to have a single bite."
今、私は恋してるの！
"Right now, I'm in love!"
はい！ということで、みんなー！
"Yes! So, everyone..."
こんこんこんこん、こんあずきー！
"Kon-kon-kon-kon, Kon-AZKi~!"
右手にマイク、左手に地図、あなたのハートをゼロゲッサー！AZKiでーす！
"Mic in my right hand, map in my left, zero-guessing your heart! I'm AZKi!"
ということで
"So..."
本日は「AZKi 7th Birthday Live Sweet Pop Story」に
"Thank you all so much for coming today to"
お越しくださり、ありがとうございます！
"'AZKi 7th Birthday Live Sweet Pop Story'!"
わーい！わーい！始まった始まったー！
"Yay! Yay! It started, it's started!"
なんと活動を始めて、7回目の誕生日を迎えることができましたー！
"I'm celebrating my 7th birthday since starting my VTuber activities!"
本当に本当に、いつも応援してくれる開拓者のみんなのおかげで、
"Really, truly, thanks to all the Pioneers who always support me,"
今日が、この日があると思っています。いつもありがとー！
"I'm able to reach this day. Thank you as always!"
ということで、なんとね、もう今日は冒頭から...
"So, amazingly, right from the start today..."
じゃじゃーん！新衣装お披露目でございます！
"Ta-da! It's my new outfit reveal!"
どうかな？どうかな？どうかな？どうどうどうどうどうどう？
"How is it? What do you think? What do you think?"
はい！今回の新衣装のテーマはですね...
"Yes! The theme for this new outfit is..."
ゆるふわ私服衣装となっております！
"a fluffy, casual clothing outfit!"
可愛いでしょう？可愛いでしょう？
"Isn't it cute? Isn't it cute?"
はい！ということでね、こういう私服っぽくて可愛い衣装が
"Yes! So, I really wanted a cute, casual outfit like this,"
いいなぁ、欲しいなぁって思っていたので、今回お仕立ていただきましたー！
"so I had it made for this live stream!"
そしてね、今日のこのライブステージも、この衣装に合わせて...
"And today's live stage was also matched to this outfit..."
なんとなんと、見てください、皆さん！
"Look, everyone!"
ちょっとお部屋っぽく、ちょっとなんかデートもできそうな...
"It's like a cozy room, perfect for going on a date..."
ステージになっております！ね、この新衣装にピッタリなステージになってます！
"...stage setup! It's a stage that fits this new outfit perfectly!"
はい！ということで、今日はね、この配信のハッシュタグ、
"Yes! So today, the hashtag for this stream is"
右上こちら！これこれこれこれこれ！
"right up here! This one right here!"
「#AZKi生誕ライブ2025」で、たくさんたくさんポストしてください！
"Please post lots with '#AZKi生誕ライブ2025'!"
スクショとか感想とか、全部全部AZKiもチェックしますので！
"I'll be checking all your screenshots and thoughts!"
可愛いAZKiをスクショするんだ！よろしくね！お願いします！
"Take screenshots of cute AZKi! Please do!"
え、そしてそして、今日はですね、新衣装のお披露目だけでなく...
"And, today isn't just a new outfit reveal..."
重大発表もありますので！
"there's also a major announcement!"
ぜひ最後まで見てください！よろしくね！
"So please watch until the end! Thank you!"
はい！ということでね、早速ライブが始まったわけなんですが...
"Yes! So, the live performance has already begun..."
ま、ちょっと今回は「Sweet Pop Story」ということで...
"and since this time it's 'Sweet Pop Story'..."
物語風にね、ちょっとデートなんかしてみちゃったり...
"it's styled like a story, having a date and all..."
はい！してね、今日のライブ楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！
"Yes! I hope you enjoy today's live performance!"
1曲目は「恋愛サーキュレーション」
"The first song was 'Ren'ai Circulation'..."
そして、2曲目は「ヒトクチ、チョウダイ？」というね、オリジナル曲でございました！
"and the second song was my original song, 'Hitokuchi, Choudai?'!"
どうだったかな？どうだった？可愛かった？
"How was it? What did you think? Was it cute?"
ということで、ここからなんと！みんなお待ちかねのゲストブロックになります！
"So from here on, it's time for the long-awaited guest segment!"
大好きなあのメンバーと可愛い曲を歌っちゃいますので...
"I'll be singing cute songs with a member I love so much..."
ぜひぜひ楽しんでいただけたらと思います！
"so I hope you all really enjoy it!"
それでは行くよ！どうぞ！
"Here we go! Enjoy!"
心予報  作詞・作曲：Eve
"[Song: Heart Forecast - Lyrics/Music: Eve]"
浮つく甘い街の喧騒
"The sweet bustle of the restless city"
故に感情線は渋滞
"Thus, the emotional lines are jammed"
「僕に関係ない」とか言って
"Saying things like 'It has nothing to do with me'"
心模様 白く染まって
"My inner feeling gets painted in white"
だけどどうやったって釣り合わない
"But no matter what, we just don't match"
いたずらに笑う横顔に乾杯
"Cheers to your profile smiling mischievously"
酸いも甘いもわからないの
"I don't know the sour or sweet of life yet"
きっと君の前では迷子
"I'm surely lost in front of you"
溶かしてはランデブー
"Melting away in a rendezvous"
プラトニックになってく
"Turning platonic"
ほろ苦い期待 張り裂けてしまいそう
"Bittersweet expectations feel like they'll burst"
だから
"So..."
夢惑う...
"Bewildered by dreams..."
想いならば
If it's your feelings,
聞かせて
let me hear them.
その声を
Let me hear that voice.
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I'm dyed in your colors, completely dyed...
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Play with my heart, don't look away.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking of you, keep thinking of you.
桃色の心予報
A pink-colored heart forecast.
今 混ざってしまえば 混ざってしまえば
If we blend together right now, completely blend...
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you, our eyes meeting with love...
ロマンスは止まらない
Romance just won't stop.
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神さまどうか今日は味方して
Dear God, please be on my side today.
おかしな君は笑って
You laugh in that charming, silly way of yours,
逆さま世界が顔出して
and an upside-down world peeked out.
夢ならまだ覚めないで
If this is a dream, don't wake me up yet.
心模様 赤に染まってく
The weather of my heart is turning red.
冷静沈着では
Being calm and composed...
どう頑張ったって無い
...no matter how hard I try, I just can't be.
大体 視界に居ない
Most of the time, you're not in my sight,
ちょっとlateなスターリナイト
a slightly late starry night.
最低な昨日にさえ
Even to the worst yesterday,
さよなら言いたいよな
I want to say goodbye.
甘いおまじないかけられてしまいそう
It feels like a sweet spell is being cast on me.
だから
That's why,
この夜を越えてゆけ
let's go beyond this night!
響かせて その想いを
Let those feelings resound.
君に染まってしまえば Ah
If I'm dyed in your colors... Ah!
君だけ想っていたいな Ah
I just want to think only of you... Ah!
君に染まってしまえば 染まってしまえば
If I'm dyed in your colors, completely dyed...
心遊ばせ 余所見しないで
Play with my heart, don't look away.
想っていたいな 想っていたいな
I want to keep thinking of you, keep thinking of you.
桃色の心予報
A pink-colored heart forecast.
今 伝えてしまえ 伝えてしまえば
If I tell you right now, if I just tell you...
君と重なって 視線が愛 相まって
Overlapping with you, our eyes meeting with love...
失敗したらグッバイステップ
If I fail, it's a goodbye step.
神さまどうか今日は味方して
Dear God, please be on my side today.
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love with me! Definitely fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating everything about you!
朝からビターなキモチ
Feeling bitter since the morning.
だって知らない表情で笑った
Because you smiled with a face I'd never seen before.
ちょっと髪に触れたりしちゃって
Touching her hair just a little bit,
なんでハナの下伸ばしてんの！？
why are you grinning like that?!
どんどん膨れていくジェラシー
This jealousy keeps swelling up,
スフレみたいに甘くないよ
it's not sweet like a soufflé!
胸いっぱいに溢れちゃって
My chest is brimming full,
ダメダメ！気付かれちゃうよ
oh no, no! You're going to notice!
バレないように…でも気付いて！フクザツな乙女心
Trying not to show it... but notice me! A maiden's complex heart.
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」
"Fall in love with me! Definitely fall in love!"
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating everything about you!
恋心 ちょっとキャラメリゼ
A romantic heart, caramelize it a little!
焦がしたらきっとスキにさせるから！
If I sear it, I'll definitely make you fall for me!
今日は朝からちょっとラッキー
Today I got a little lucky since morning.
あくびこらえた変顔見ちゃった
I caught you making a funny face trying to hold a yawn.
肩たたきながら「おはよう」なんて言えたらもっと
If I could tap your shoulder and say "Good morning", that'd be great, but...
あぁ！もう！イケナイ！
Ah! Jeez! I can't do that!
ふぅ…ちょっと落ち着いて？
Phew... calm down a bit, okay?
モンテしすぎて漏れちゃうよ
Whipping it up too much, it's gonna spill over!
「なにしてんの？」ってほっぺツンツン
Asking "What're you doing?" as you poke my cheek,
いきなりまさかの不意打ち禁止～！！
sudden surprise attacks like that are forbidden!!
メレンゲハート 耳までキュイール アツいのは私だけ？
Meringue heart, baked to the ears... Am I the only one feeling hot?
スキすぎる！あぁ…スキすぎる！
I love you too much! Ah... I love you so much!
ココロから スペシャリテのアイラヴユー
From the bottom of my heart, a specialty "I love you"!
恋心 もっとタブラーージュ
A romantic heart, temper it even more!
溶けたなら ハート型にグラッセしよう
Once melted, let's glaze it into a heart shape!
アナタにだけ教えてあげる
I'll teach only you...
このキモチのヒミツ
...the secret of these feelings.
「ダイスキだよ！」
"I love you so much!"
「スキになれ！ぜったいスキになれ！」おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
"Fall in love with me! Definitely fall in love!" A magic spell, decorating everything about you!
おまじない アナタごとデコレーション
A magic spell, decorating all of you
このキモチ ずっとアラカルト
These feelings, forever à la carte
おすそわけ ココロごとデコレーション
Sharing with you, decorating heart and all
恋心 いっぱいプレゼント
A present packed full of love
届いたら 私ごと召し上がれ♪
When it reaches you, eat me up entirely♪
Lalala...♪
ほめのび
[Title: Homenobi]
なーにしよっか練習中
What should I do? Practicing now
しれっとこそっと準備進行
Secretly and nonchalantly making progress
心境 緊張 で焦る
Nervous mindset, feeling flustered
言わんけどつよつよアリでしょ？
I won't say it, but being super strong is great, right?
元気配るから待っちょって
I'll share my energy, so hold on
そうやって成長する子です
That's how I grow as a person
いいかな？
Is that okay?
ゆるポンでOK？
Is being easygoing and goofy OK?
いちにーさん
One, two, three
テンパっちゃってOK？
Is panicking OK?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
Praise me, I want you to praise me
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll work 20% harder
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
Watch me, I want you to watch me
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type who thrives when showered with praise
もう
Jeez
なぁーんにも出てこない
Nothing is coming to mind at all
頭ん中真っ白だ
My head is completely blank
さっぱりだ うんうんあれ？
Clueless... Yeah, wait, what?
まっいっか
Oh well, whatever!
凸凹な情緒 提供中
Serving up bumpy emotions right now
ぽかんとして何しちょんの
Standing there blankly, what are you doing?
こんなが通常のわたし
This is just the normal me
いいでしょ
Pretty good, right?
それではOK？
So, is everything OK?
いちにーさん
One, two, three
落ち着きOK？
Feeling calm enough, OK?
始めちゃおう
Let's get started
どうしたらいいの？ どうしたらいいの？
What should I do? What should I do?
どうすればみんなハッピーで笑顔バッチリ
How can everyone be happy with perfect smiles?
こちらへどうぞ こちらへどうぞ
Right this way please, right this way please
押さず慌てず並んで合図です
Don't push, don't rush, line up on cue
もう
Jeez
聞こえてる？
Can you hear me?
(みゃっみゃっみゃー)
(Mya, mya, mya)
楽しんでる？
Are you enjoying yourself?
(ぽんぽんぽん) こっちだよ
(Pon, pon, pon) Over here!
少し眠いな 少し眠いな
A bit sleepy, a bit sleepy
また明日食べて寝て今は成長期
Eat and sleep again tomorrow, I'm in my growth period
夢を見たいな 夢を見たいな
I want to dream, I want to dream
どうぞくれぐれもあの...今後も
Please, by all means, um... in the future too
ほめてほしいな ほめてほしいな
Praise me, I want you to praise me
ほめてくれたら2割増しでがんばる
If you praise me, I'll work 20% harder
見ててほしいな 見ててほしいな
Watch me, I want you to watch me
ほめちぎられて伸びるタイプです
I'm the type who thrives when showered with praise
またね
See you later
sweet night, sweet time...
[Title: sweet night, sweet time...]
ぜっと 陽の沈む 茜の空
Gently, the sun sets into the crimson sky
やっと 目覚めた きみに挨拶
Finally awake, I greet you
えっと 明日は 休みだから
Um, tomorrow is a day off, so
一晩中 きみと一緒に
All night long, together with you
sweet night, sweet time...
眠くないよ 眠くないの
I'm not sleepy, I'm not sleepy
sweet night, sweet time…
まだまだ遊びたい
I still want to play more
sweet night, sweet time…
話したいよ 話し足りないの
I want to talk, I haven't talked enough
夢の中じゃ 物足りないから
Because in dreams, it's just not enough
今夜は…
Tonight...
寝なーい 眠らない
Won't sleep, not sleeping
きみとリズム合わせ
Matching rhythm with you
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
Enjoying turning day and night upside down
今だけ…
Just for now...
寝なーい 眠らない
Won't sleep, not sleeping
星のなか散歩して
Strolling through the stars
夜がどうか 明けないように
Praying the night won't dawn
いつまでも
Forever and ever
きっと話すのも 笑うのも
Surely, talking and laughing
もっと誰かとつながるため
Are all to connect more with someone
ちょっと俯いたきみへ向けて
Facing toward you who looked down a bit
一晩中歌ってもいい
It's fine to sing all night long
sweet night, sweet time…
眠らないよ 眠らないの
I won't sleep, I'm not sleeping
sweet night, sweet time…
夜ごと遊びたい
I want to play every night
sweet night, sweet time…
喋りたいよ 喋り足りないの
I want to chat, I haven't chatted enough
sweet night, sweet time…
きみと朝まで
With you until morning
月も知らない
Without even the moon knowing
ナイショ話を
A secret conversation
パジャマのままで
Still in our pajamas
お願い
Please
夢の中じゃ物足りないから
Because in dreams, it's just not enough
もう少し…
Just a little more...
寝なーい 眠らない
Won't sleep, not sleeping
きみとリズム合わせ
Matching rhythm with you
昼夜逆転を楽しむの
Enjoying turning day and night upside down
今だけ…
Just for now...
寝なーい 眠らない
Won't sleep, not sleeping
白む空見送って
Watching the whitening sky go by
夜を越えよう
Let's cross through the night
また明日も
Tomorrow too
ここで会おう
Let me meet you here
また明日
See you tomorrow
good night, good time…
というわけで、ゲストブロックをお送りしましたー！
And with that, we've brought you the guest section!
どうだったかな？どうだったかな？
How was it? How was it?
はい、ということでゲストパートなんですが、ここまでを振り返ると…
Yes! So, looking back on everything in the guest section so far...
えー、いろはちゃんと『心予報』をお届けしました！
Um, Iroha-chan and I performed "Kokoro Yohou"!
なんとね、いろはちゃんの新衣装3Dでね
Amazingly, with Iroha-chan's new 3D outfit,
一緒にこれは「あずいろてぇてぇ」を…あずいろてぇてぇをしたいと思って
I wanted us to share some sweet AzuIro moments together,
えー、一緒に歌ってみたも出した『心予報』を…
so we sang "Kokoro Yohou", which we also released a cover video of,
ちょっと踊って一緒にこの新衣装であずいろてぇてぇしました。
danced a bit, and shared wholesome AzuIro moments in her new outfit!
どうだった？どうだった？良かったでしょう？
How was it? How was it? It was great, right?
え、そして、次はラミィちゃんと『初恋パティシエール』という…
And next, with Lamy-chan, "Hatsukoi Pattissiere"...
ラミィちゃんのオリ曲をね、もうこの、このライブのテーマに絶対に合うと思って…
which is Lamy-chan's original song, thinking it would definitely suit the theme of this live...
一緒に歌わせていただきました！可愛かった！
I had the pleasure of singing it with her! It was so cute!
え、そしてそして、え、団長と『ほめのび』！
And then, and then... with Danchou, "Homenobi"!
これはね、ずっとずっとAZKi一緒に団長と『ほめのび』を歌うのが夢だったんで…
You know, it was always AZKi's dream to sing "Homenobi" together with Danchou...
もうこのライブで実現するぞと思って、えー、『ほめのび』で成長していきたいと…甘えます！
so I realized that dream at this live, wanting to grow through "Homenobi"... I'm pampering myself!
え、そしてそして、え、わためと一緒に、え、わためのオリジナル曲『sweet night, sweet time...』を歌わせていただきました！
And then, together with Watame, I got to sing Watame's original song, "sweet night, sweet time..."!
もうこれもね、今回のコンセプトにめちゃくちゃ合う、あ、わためとこの曲一緒に歌いたいなぁと思って選曲しました！
This one too fit the concept of this live so well, so I picked it thinking I really wanted to sing it with Watame!
どうだったかなー？
How was it?
いやー、嬉しいね！ホロメンのオリ曲歌ったりできるの、本当にライブならではという感じて…
Man, I'm so happy! Being able to sing Hololive members' original songs really feels like something special only a live concert can bring...
えー、お送りしましたが、まだまだゲストパート続きますので…
And with that, we've delivered these songs, but the guest section still continues...
えー、セットリストのAZKiさんにもご注目ください！
so please keep an eye on setlist creator AZKi-san as well!
ということで、まだまだゲストパートいくぞー！
So, moving right along into more of the guest section, let's go!
尻尾ふってスカウト
Wagging our tails to scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering even more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
Once we gather up, we're the strongest!
文化祭が始まる
The school festival is starting!
最大規模でいきたいの
We want to do it on the grandest scale!
君も参加してよね
You better join in too!
ネットチケット無制限
Unlimited online tickets!
校長先生もビックリ
Even the principal is shocked!
キャスト足んない 大焦り
Not enough cast members, total panic!
ワンワン泣いちゃう うぅ
Crying like a puppy, boo-hoo!
本番間近 胃はキリキリ
Close to the show, stomach aching!
運営の予算はギリギリ
Management's budget is cutting it close!
すねちゃうぞ 泣いちゃうぞ
I'll pout! I'll cry!
テレフォンナンバー ぴ ぴ ぴ ぴ
Telephone number, beep beep beep beep!
「イケてる子を用意して」
"Get some cool girls ready!"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello hello, I'm the organizer!
可愛い子 チェック！スカウトー！
Cute girls, check! Scout!
超超超！超順調！美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
Super super super! Super smooth sailing! Got a pretty girl!☆
美少女捕まえた☆
Caught a pretty girl!☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to die...
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Make my virtual funeral super flashy!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how seriously I want to do this!
尻尾ふってスカウト
Wagging our tails to scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering even more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
Once we gather up, we're the strongest!
あー無駄足三昧しんどいわ
Ah, so tiring running around in vain!
どうしようもない焦燥感
Helpless feeling of impatience
タイムリミットは後ちょっと！？
Is the time limit almost up?!
ここらでもういっちょ！
Let's give it another go right here!
美味しいころね食べたら
Once you eat delicious Korone,
犬に金棒最強よ
An iron club to a dog, ultimate strength!
東西南北 駆け回り
Running all around, East, West, North, and South!
まだ見ぬあの子 探し出せ！
Find that girl we haven't seen yet!
ワンワン吠いちゃう わおん
Barking like a dog, woof!
呼んだらどこでも駆けつけます！
Call us and we'll rush over anywhere!
いい子がいたら、教えてね
If there's a good girl, let us know!
噛んじゃうぞ 甘えちゃうぞ
I'll bite you! I'll act spoiled!
テレフォンナンバー ぴ ぴ ぴ ぴ
Telephone number, beep beep beep beep!
「イケてる子が見つかった？」
"Did you find a cool girl?"
もしもし私オーガナイザー
Hello hello, I'm the organizer!
可愛い子 チェック！スカウトー！
Cute girls, check! Scout!
超超超！超順調！美少女ゲットだぜっ☆
Super super super! Super smooth sailing! Got a pretty girl!☆
美少女捕まえた☆
Caught a pretty girl!☆
もしも私が死んだなら
If I were to die...
バーチャル葬でド派手にねっ
Make my virtual funeral super flashy!
それくらい私本気でやりたいの
That's how seriously I want to do this!
尻尾ふってスカウト
Wagging our tails to scout
可愛い子もっとエンカウント
Encountering even more cute girls
集まっちゃえば最強よ！
Once we gather up, we're the strongest!
自薦他薦は問いません
Self-nominations and recommendations welcome!
「私、君を待ってるよ」
"I'm waiting for you!"
うー あー もう はい
Ooh... Ah... Gosh... Yes!
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No way, no way, I can't afford to mess up, right?
真っ赤なハート差し出して…そんなのやっぱ妄想じゃん
Holding out a bright red heart... that's just a delusion after all.
そっちはどう思ってるの 言いかけてしまう無理みたい
What do you think over there? I start to ask, but it seems impossible.
こんなんじゃ…ってわかってるんだ 思った以上にハマっていくんだ
I know this is no good... but I'm falling deeper than I thought.
頑張りたいあたしに期待 ぎゅーだってしたいかも…かもん
Hoping for a me who wants to try hard, might even want a tight hug... Come on!
ちょっとは変われていますか？ 足りないとこばっかだけど
Have I changed even a little bit? Though I'm full of flaws...
ポンでコツでドジじゃないあたしだったら きみはだめだよね？
If I weren't clumsy, airheaded, and goofy, you wouldn't like me, right?
ねぇもうやだやだ ミスってらんない
Hey, no way, no way, I can't afford to mess up.
もうやだやだ 踊ってベイビィダンス
No way, no way, dancing the Baby Dance.
あたしはまだ諦めない でもでも全然だめかも
I still won't give up, but hey, maybe it's totally useless.
だってベイビィダンス うまくできないの
Because with the Baby Dance, I can't do it right.
だってベイビィダンス 伝えられないの
Because with the Baby Dance, I can't convey my feelings.
もっと可愛くなりたいのに どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
Even though I want to become cuter, I don't know what I should do.
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No way, no way, I can't afford to mess up, right?
あ〜やっちまった こんなはずじゃ
Ah, I messed up, it wasn't supposed to be like this.
どうしてどうして わかっているのに
Why, oh why, even though I know...
見せたくないとこ透けちゃって
The parts I don't want to show are showing through...
無理無理 でも期待はしたいな いいですか？
Impossible, no way, but I still want to hope. Is that okay?
ポンもコツもドジも全部あたしなんだよ ちゃんとみていてほしい
Being clumsy, airheaded, and goofy is all me, I want you to look at me properly.
ねぇもうやだやだ ぐずって後悔
Hey, no way, no way, sulking and regretting.
もうやだやだ 回ってベイビィダンス
No way, no way, spinning around in the Baby Dance.
だめなあたし塗り替えたい でもでも全然だめかも
I want to remake this useless me, but hey, maybe it's totally useless.
だってベイビィダンス うまくできないの
Because with the Baby Dance, I can't do it right.
だってベイビィダンス 伝えられないの
Because with the Baby Dance, I can't convey my feelings.
もっと可愛くなりたいのに どうしたらいいとかわかんないし
Even though I want to become cuter, I don't know what I should do.
まだまだいけるかな
I wonder if I can still keep going...
まだまだ言えるかな
I wonder if I can still say it...
まだまだできるかな
I wonder if I can still do it...
まだまだ… うぅ…
Still... ooh...
ポンでコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかって
I'm clumsy, airheaded, hopeless, and full of flaws, but...
きっとやめないんだ
I'm definitely not quitting!
ポンでコツでドジでだめで足りないとこばっかって
I'm clumsy, airheaded, hopeless, and full of flaws, but...
見ていてほしい
I want you to keep watching me!
ねぇもうやだやだ ミスってらんない
Hey, no more mistakes, I can't mess up!
もうやだやだ 踊ってベイビー・ダンス
No more, no more! Dance, Baby Dance!
あたしはまだ諦めない ほらほら 全然だめじゃない
I won't give up yet! Look, look, I'm not useless at all!
だってベイビー・ダンス うまくできるから
'Cause with Baby Dance, I can do it right!
だってベイビー・ダンス 伝えられるから
'Cause with Baby Dance, I can get it across!
もっと可愛くなりたいから どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
I want to become even cuter, so I can try my best no matter what!
だってベイビー・ダンス きみに届くまで
'Cause with Baby Dance, until it reaches you...
だってベイビー・ダンス きみに会えるまで
'Cause with Baby Dance, until I can see you...
もっと可愛くなりたいから どんな時だってそう 頑張れるし
I want to become even cuter, so I can try my best no matter what!
やだやだ ミスってらんない、ね？
No, no, I can't afford to mess up, right?
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Surprise Service
We are スティーレ！
We are Stile!
さあ 扉を開けて
Come on, open the door...
未知なるパラダイス
...to an unknown paradise!
体験しよう おいでYOU
Let's experience it! Come on in, YOU!
そう キミを待つのは
Yes, what awaits you...
不思議なオアシス
...is a mysterious oasis!
ほっこり日常に
Add a little spice...
ちょっぴりSpice
...to your cozy everyday life!
ぐーるんぐーるん かきまぜちゃうんだ
Swirling round and round, mixing it up!
ぐーるんぐーるん 当店自慢のフレイバー
Swirling round and round, our cafe's pride flavor!
サービス サービス ご褒美タイム
Service, service, reward time!
おもてなし ココロこめて
Welcoming you with all our heart!
Welcome to... わーい！ わたし達と一緒に
Welcome to... Yay! Together with us...
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
...a dazzling wonder daydream!
愛情マシマシ
Extra affection...
煩悩ナデナデ
...patting away worldly desires...
誠心誠意 つとめます
...serving you with pure sincerity!
いえーす！ キミの元気チャージに ひと役かえるかな
Yes! Can we help recharge your energy?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも 意外と悪くないでしょ？
This kind of vibe or that kind of vibe, it's surprisingly not bad, right?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, Buono, want to blend it!
きゅんきゅんきゅん ハートに ばんちばんちばんち
Kyun-kyun-kyun! Punching right into your heart!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, Buono, want to blend it!
お口にあいますか？
Is it to your liking?
お口にあうといいな♪
Hope you enjoy the taste♪
ぼなぺてぃーと
Bon Appetit!
ぼなぺてぃーと？
Bon Appetit?
千客ばんばんらーい！
A booming trade with overflowing customers!
ちょっと、なんか、不本意ながらも
Hey, somehow, even if it's reluctant...
いつだって需要は斜め上
...demand always exceeds expectations!
そんじゃいいか ホントのわたしは
Oh well, the real me is...
シークレットモードで 営業スイッチオン
...in secret mode, switching on business mode!
ぐーるんぐーるん かきまぜてもっと
Swirling round and round, mix it up even more!
ぐーるんぐーるん キミ仕様のフレイバー
Swirling round and round, a flavor customized just for you!
サービス サービス 極上タイム
Service, service, supreme quality time!
癒やしとは かくあるべき
This is how true comfort should be!
Welcome to... わーい！ わたし達のお店に
Welcome to... Yay! To our café...
本日もようこそ
...welcome today as well!
おかえり待ってた リピートうれしいな
Welcome back, we've been waiting! So happy you returned!
店員一同 歓迎
All staff welcome you!
いえーす！ キミのお疲れさまに ピッタリのレシピで
Yes! With the perfect recipe for your hard work...
こーいうのどうかな あーいうのアリかな よろこんでもらえてるかな
How about this? Is that okay? Hope it brings a smile to your face!
Smile
Sweet
Sister
Sadistic
Strange, Serious, Selfish, Secret, Supercar...
We are スティーレ！
We are Stile!
さあ 扉を開けて
Come on, open the door...
愉快なパラダイス
...to a delightful paradise!
怖がらずにおいで おいで
Don't be afraid, come on in!
そう いつも通りの毎日に
Yes, into your usual everyday life...
イロドリと アソビゴコロ 召し上がれ
...enjoy a serving of color and playfulness!
ブレンド・S
Blend S!
Welcome to... わーい！ わたし達と一緒に
Welcome to... Yay! Together with us...
めくるめくワンダーデイドリーム
...a dazzling wonder daydream!
愛情マシマシ
Extra affection...
煩悩ナデナデ
...patting away worldly desires...
誠心誠意 つとめます
...serving you with pure sincerity!
いえーす！ キミの元気チャージに ひと役かえるかな
Yes! Can we help recharge your energy?
こーいった感じも あーいった感じも 意外と悪くないでしょ？
This kind of vibe or that kind of vibe, it's surprisingly not bad, right?
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, Buono, want to blend it!
きゅんきゅんきゅん ぱんちぱんちぱんち
Kyun-kyun-kyun! Punching right into your heart!
Buono Buono ブレンドしたい
Buono, Buono, I want to blend it.
お口にあいますか？
Does it suit your taste?
お好み聞かせてね
Tell me what you like.
お口にあうといいな
I hope it suits your taste.
というわけで、引き続きゲストブロックをお送りしましたー！
And with that, we've brought you another guest segment!
どうだったかなー？どうだったかなー？
How was it? How was it?
はい！ということでこの後はですね、重大発表もございますので、ぜひ最後まで見てねー！
Yes! So after this, we have some major announcements, so please watch until the very end!
はい、そんなゲストブロックの後半なんですが、コロさんと「可愛子チェック」で尻尾フリフリしましたー！
Yes! In the second half of the guest segment, Korone-san and I did 'Kawaiko Check' and wagged our tails!
そして、みこちと「Baby Dance」をお送りしましたー！一緒になんか私服衣装でシナジーあったんじゃないかなって思いました。
And then, Miko-chi and I performed 'Baby Dance'! Doing it together in our casual outfits gave us great synergy, I think.
革そしてそして、フワモコちゃんと「ぼなぺてぃーと♡S」をお届けしましたー！
And then, FuwaMoco and I brought you 'Bon Appétit♡S'!
いやー、フワモコちゃんとね、一緒にね、こうやって3Dライブしたいなーって思ってたので
I really wanted to do a 3D live with FuwaMoco like this,
念願念願叶って、あずきのやりたいことを全部全部詰め込んだゲストパートでございましたー！
so my long-cherished wish came true! This guest segment was packed with everything AZKi wanted to do!
はい！ということで、ま、重大発表もあるんですけど
Yes! So, while we do have major announcements...
その前に！皆さん、あのお知らせがございます！
Before that, everyone! I have THAT announcement for you!
AZKi生誕記念2025グッズ販売告知ー！こちらをご覧ください！
AZKi Birthday Celebration 2025 Merchandise Sale Announcement! Please take a look at this!
うわー！今回もダダダンと盛りだくさんでございます！
Woah! This time as well, it's packed full of goods!
今回イラストはD福先生に描いていただきました！ありがとうございます！
The illustrations this time were drawn by D-Fuku-sensei! Thank you so much!
それでは詳細を見ていきましょう！まずはこちら！
Now then, let me give you all the details! First up is this!
ダダダン！抱き枕カバー！ということで、今回のゆるふわな私服の衣装で寝転がっている
Tada! Body Pillow Cover! A body pillow cover of AZKi lying down in this soft casual outfit...
AZKiの抱き枕カバーが出ます！うわー！
...is coming out! Woah!
まさかグッズになるとは思いもしませんでしたので、ぜひチェックしてください！
I never imagined it would become merch, so please be sure to check it out!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
缶バッジセットー！こちらね、ハートの形をした缶バッジとなっております。
Button Badge Set! These are heart-shaped button badges.
キラキラのホログラム仕様となっておりますので、いっぱい一杯ね、つけてほしいなと思います。
They have a sparkly hologram finish, so I hope you attach them everywhere!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
開拓者ぬいぐるみキーホルダー！
Pioneer Plush Keychain!
ということで、ホロライブフレンズとぅーごーのAZKiと大体同じくらいのちっちゃいサイズになってますんで
It's roughly the same small size as the Hololive Friends with u AZKi plush,
一緒に持ち歩いてもらえるようなサイズ感となっておりますので
making it the perfect size to carry around with you wherever you go.
一緒にね、AZKiと開拓者ぬいで、お出かけしてほしいなと思います！
I hope you go on trips together with AZKi and the Pioneer plush!
続いてはこちら！
Next up is this!
開拓者アイマスク！
Pioneer Eye Mask!
今回抱き枕カバーと一緒に、もうね、安眠できるグッズをご用意いたしましたので、こちらもぜひ寝る時に使ってほしいなと思います！
Along with the body pillow cover, we prepared merch to ensure a good night's sleep, so I hope you use this when sleeping too!
そして続いてはこちら！
And next up is this!
ASMRボイス！ボイスタイトルは『AZKiのわがままをきいて』というね
ASMR Voice! The title is 'Listen to AZKi's Selfish Requests'.
ちょっとAZKiがちょっとしたわがままを言って、君をデートに誘うシチュエーションとなっておりますので
It's a scenario where AZKi makes a little selfish request and invites you on a date,
今回のこのゆるふわ私服衣装のAZKiを思い浮かべて聴いてください！
so please picture AZKi in this soft casual outfit while listening!
そして、フルセット購入特典もございます！こちら！
And we also have a full set purchase bonus! Here it is!
なんと数量限定版はAZKiの直筆サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと、特典ASMRボイス、タイトルは『寝起きのアズキと』ということで
The limited quantity version includes a handwritten autographed bromide card by AZKi, and a bonus ASMR voice titled 'Waking Up with AZKi'!
こちらね、抱き枕カバーの裏面のイラストをイメージしたシチュエーションとなっておりますので、こちらも一緒に楽しんでいただけたらなと思います！
This scenario is inspired by the illustration on the back of the body pillow cover, so I hope you enjoy this as well!
そして数量限定が無くなり次第、箔押しの複製サイン入りチェキ風ブロマイドカードと特典ASMRボイス
And once the limited quantity sells out, it will be a foil-stamped duplicate signature bromide card and bonus ASMR voice,
同様の『寝起きのアズキと』となっておりますので、よろしくお願いします！
with the same track 'Waking Up with AZKi', so please keep that in mind!
改めてフルセットはこちらとなります！ジャン！
Once again, here is the complete full set! Ta-da!
いやー、いっぱいありますねー！買うならね、やっぱフルセットがいいですよ！みんなよろしくね、この後！
There's so much included! If you're buying, the full set is definitely best! Everyone, please check it out!
はい！そして、さらにタレントプレミアムグッズのフルセット特典といたしまして
Yes! And as an additional bonus for the talent premium goods full set,
昨年から発売された「hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME」で使用できるカードが1枚付きます！
a card that can be used in the 'hololive OFFICIAL CARD GAME' released last year is included!
カードはホロライブプロダクションオフィシャルショップで購入された方のみ対象となります。
This card applies only to those who purchase from the Hololive Production Official Shop.
特典につくのは推しをアピールできるキーカード、推しホロメンカードでございます。
The bonus is an Oshi Holomen card, a key card to showcase your favorite talent!
カードの詳細や遊び方についてはホームページをご確認ください。
For card details and how to play, please check the official website.
同梱するカードは日本語版のみとなります。
Please note that the included card is available in Japanese only.
ますので ご了承ください
So please keep that in mind!
以上 AZKi誕生日記念2025のグッズ情報でした
That was the goods information for AZKi Birthday Commemoration 2025!
みんな買ってね ぜひ
Everyone, please buy them! Be sure to!
よろしくお願いします
Thank you so much!
ということで お待たせいたしました
And with that, thank you for waiting!
さらに重大発表ございます
Furthermore, we have a major announcement!
それではお待たせいたしました
So, thank you for waiting.
こちらをご覧ください
Please take a look at this!
重大発表
[Major Announcement]
はい
Yes!
ということで AZKiの新しいEP『Re://Start』と『Re://Birth』が
So, AZKi's new EPs, "Re://Start" and "Re://Birth",
11月5日にリリースすることが決定いたしました！
are set to be released on November 5th!
今回は初めてとなる2作同時リリースとなっております
This time, for the first time, it's a simultaneous release of two works!
この後21時より hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPと
Pre-orders will start today from 21:00 on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP
全国のCDショップで予約が開始されます！
and CD shops nationwide!
そして1枚目の『Re://Start』には
And the first disc, "Re://Start", contains
AZKiの新しい魅力が詰まった新曲4曲
four new songs filled with AZKi's new charm!
2枚目の『Re://Birth』には
The second disc, "Re://Birth", features
イノナカミュージック時代の楽曲4曲のリアレンジバージョンが収録されます
re-arranged versions of four songs from her INONAKA MUSIC era!
そしてCD限定特典として それぞれボーナストラックに
And as a CD-exclusive bonus, each disc includes a bonus track,
すいちゃんと歌った『The Last Frontier』が1種類ずつ収録されます
a different version of "The Last Frontier" sung with Sui-chan!
また 通常版には限定特典として ランダムアナザージャケットが1枚ついてきます
Also, the regular edition comes with a random alternative jacket cover as an exclusive bonus!
なんとこちらには数量限定で 私の直筆サイン入りが入っているかもとのことです
And apparently, a limited quantity of these might even include my handwritten signature!
各種CDショップでの購入特典はこちらです
Here are the purchase bonuses for various CD shops!
特典の絵柄は後日発表します
The artwork for the bonuses will be announced at a later date!
さらに hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPでは
Furthermore, on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP,
セットになったコンプリート盤を発売します
we will be releasing a complete box set!
コンプリート盤にはここでしか手に入らない たくさんの特典もついております
The complete set comes with many exclusive bonuses that you can only get here!
数に限りがございますので お早めに
Quantities are limited, so please order early!
そして1点
And one more point!
hololive production OFFICIAL SHOPのアルバム購入について注意事項がございます
There is an important notice regarding album purchases on the hololive production OFFICIAL SHOP.
完全生産限定コンプリート盤は 発売日でのお届けとなりますので
Since the Limited Complete Edition will be delivered on the release date,
EP以外のグッズとの商品は同時購入できません
it cannot be purchased together with non-EP merchandise!
通常版は他のグッズとの同時購入が可能ですが
The regular edition can be purchased alongside other merchandise,
店頭販売日以降のお届けになる可能性があるので こちらご注意ください
but please note that delivery may be after the store release date!
詳しくは販売サイトの注意事項をご確認ください
Please check the notes on the store page for details!
はい そして最後に もう一つお知らせあります
Yes! And finally, I have one more announcement!
今回発表したこのニューEP『Re://Start』の中から
From the new EP "Re://Start" announced today,
『未来カンパネラ』という楽曲を
the song titled "Mirai Campanella"
本日24時にデジタルリリースします！
will be digitally released at midnight tonight!
わー！新曲だー！
Yay! A new song!
配信終了後にはミュージックビデオもプレミア公開しちゃいます！ということで
After the stream ends, the music video will also premiere! So...
ぜひチェックしてください！
be sure to check it out!
いっぱい情報がありましたが みんなついてこられましたか？
That was a lot of information, was everyone able to keep up?
はい
Alright!
ということで ライブも次の曲で最後になります
So, with that, the concert will come to an end with the next song.
最後はAZKiの新しい曲を聴いていただきたいと思います
For the final song, I would like you to listen to AZKi's new song!
それでは
And now,
聴いてください 『未来カンパネラ』
please listen to "Mirai Campanella".
もっと
More...
鏡よ 教えて
Mirror, tell me,
私の証は どこにあるのだろう
where is the proof of my existence?
分から無い 分から無いよ
I don't know, I just don't know.
周りと 比べたってさ
Even if I compare myself to others,
虚しく なるだけ
it only leaves me feeling empty.
あぁ ノイズが 海鳴りの ように ナミダを 奪う
Ah, the noise strips away my tears like the roaring sea.
切り取った 風景を 道しるべに しよう
Let's turn this captured scenery into a guidepost.
そうだ 傷ついた 感情も
That's right, even these hurt feelings...
連れて行くから
I'll take you with me,
そっと響くカンパネラ 新しい未来を感じてる
The softly echoing Campanella, I feel a new future.
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ?
Even if I'm scared, I have to keep moving forward, right?
遠くまで
Far away...
届け この祈りよ 光となれ
Reach out, my prayer, become the light!
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい 「私」という答えを
More, more, even little by little is okay, the answer that is "me"...
もっと もっと...
More, more...
夜空よ教えて 私の証は 輝けるのかな
Tell me, night sky, will my proof shine?
見つけたい 見つけたいよ
I want to find it, I really want to find it!
誰かの決めたレールは 苦しくなるだけ
Walking on the rails set by someone else only brings pain.
ねぇ ノイズも力に変えるよ
Hey, I'll turn even the noise into strength!
ココロに誓う
I swear to my heart,
錆びついた運命の歯車を回そう
let me turn the rusted gears of fate.
ほら 着飾った感情は 脱ぎ捨てるから
See, I'll strip away these embellished feelings.
そっと紡ぐシンフォニア 叶えたい願いを信じてる
Softly weaving a Symphonia, I believe in the wish I want to fulfill.
胸を張って歌うしかないでしょ?
Hold your head high, I have no choice but to sing, right?
全力で
With all my heart!
やがて希望の歌に変わる日まで
Until the day it turns into a song of hope,
もっと もっと 悩みながらでいい すべてが宝物
more, more, it's okay to struggle, everything is a treasure.
いつの日かこの声を 受け取ってくれたなら
If someday you accept this voice of mine,
この言葉を君に 「もう大丈夫 一人じゃない」
I'll pass these words to you: "It's alright now, you're not alone."
強い想いを繋ぐよ
I will connect these strong feelings.
一歩踏み出してみた 優しく世界は微笑む
I took a step forward, and the world smiled gently.
高鳴る気持ちに身を任せて さあ行こう
Surrendering myself to these throbbing feelings, come, let's go!
そっと響くカンパネラ 新しい未来を感じてる
The softly echoing Campanella, I feel a new future.
怖くたって進むしかないでしょ?
Even if I'm scared, I have to keep moving forward, right?
遠くまで
Far away...
届け この祈りよ 光となれ
Reach out, my prayer, become the light!
もっと もっと 少しずつでもいい 「私」という答えを
More, more, even little by little is okay, the answer that is "me"...
もっと もっと...
More, more...
ごめん、待った？
Sorry, did you wait long?
ごめんね、ライブ終わった後、マネージャーさんに呼ばれちゃって。
Sorry! After the concert, my manager called me over.
もちろん、打ち上げもあったけど、君と会うためにキャンセルしたんだからね。
Of course, there was an after-party, but I canceled it to see you!
改めて、今日はライブに来てくれてありがとう。
Once again, thank you for coming to my concert today!
アリーナ席の右の方にいたよね？
You were on the right side of the arena seats, right?
ちゃんと見つけたよ！
I totally spotted you!
実は今日、花火大会なんだって。
Actually, I heard there's a fireworks festival today.
こんな大都会で花火あがるの、ロマンチックだなあ。
Fireworks going off in a big city like this is so romantic.
ね、見て見て！今日のライブのキービジュアルだよ！
Hey, look, look! It's the key visual from today's concert!
もしかしたら、ここでも流れてたのかな？
I wonder if it was playing here too?
ついさっきのことだから、ちょっと恥ずかしいよ。
Since it was just a moment ago, it's a bit embarrassing.
でも、とっても楽しかったな。
But it was so much fun!
あ、雨？
Ah, rain?
どうしよう、私、傘持ってないよ。
What should I do? I don't have an umbrella.
あ、傘持ってきたんだ。
Ah, you brought an umbrella for me!
ありがとう。かっこいいじゃん。
Thank you! That's so cool of you.
でも、傘ひとつしか無いってことは...これって相合い傘だよね？
But... since there's only one umbrella... that means we're sharing an umbrella, right?
私、相合い傘って初めてで...これってさ...
This is my first time sharing an umbrella... So this means...
あ、ドキドキするね
Ah, my heart is pounding.
あ、雨が止んだ
Ah, the rain stopped.
通り雨だったのかな？
Was it a passing shower?
なんか... 雨止んで嬉しいような... 悲しいような...
Somehow... I'm glad it stopped, but also a bit sad...
もっと君と相合傘したかったな...
I wanted to share an umbrella with you longer...
なんてね
Just kidding!
雨も止んだし、雨で人通りも少なくなったしさ
Since the rain stopped and there aren't many people around,
グリコゲームでもしようよ
let's play the Glico game!
ここからスタートね
We'll start from here, okay?
行くよ！
Here we go!
じゃん・けん・ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
やったー！私の勝ち！
Yay! I won!
ち・よ・こ・れ・い・と！
Ch-o-co-la-te!
ちょっと何？ニヤニヤして見てるの？
Wait, what? Why are you smirking at me?
え？可愛いって？
Huh? "You're cute"?
もう... ちょっと恥ずかしいからやめてよ！
Geez... Stop it, you're making me embarrassed!
次行くよ！
Next round!
じゃん・けん・ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
ぐ・り・こ！
Gu-ri-co!
だからちょっとニヤニヤやめてってばー！
I told you, stop smirking like that!
次行くよ！
Next round!
じゃん・けん・ぽん！
Rock, paper, scissors!
ぱ・い・な・つ・ぷ・る！
Pa-i-na-pp-le!
もう、じゃんけん弱すぎだよ〜！
Geez, you're way too weak at rock-paper-scissors~!
絶対わざと負けてるでしょ！
You're definitely losing on purpose, right?
もう、いい加減にしてよね！
Come on, take it seriously!
え？何？
Huh? What?
こっち来てって？
"Come over here"?
どこ行くの？
Where are we going?
何々？見せたいものがある？
What is it? You have something to show me?
あのモニターを見ろって？
"Look at that monitor"?
3、2、1...？
3, 2, 1...?
え？え？どういうこと？
Eh? Eh? What does this mean?
お誕生日おめでとう？
Happy Birthday?
えー！ありがとうー！
Whaat! Thank you so much!
サプライズしてくれたんだ！
You prepared a surprise for me!
嬉しい！
I'm so happy!
いつも一番近くで応援してくれて、本当にありがとう！
Thank you so much for always supporting me up close!
これからもよろしくね！
Please keep supporting me from now on too!
綺麗〜！
So pretty~!
素敵な誕生日にしてくれてありがとう！
Thank you for making this such a wonderful birthday!
お礼に
As a thank you,
この後、君だけのアンコールライブするね！
I'll do an encore live just for you after this!
これからもずっと一緒にいてね！
Please stay with me forever from now on too!
今日はお誕生日お祝いしてくれてありがとう！新衣装のAZKiもよろしくね！！
[Text: Thank you for celebrating my birthday today! Please support AZKi in her new outfit too!!]
新衣装お披露目 & 重大発表あり AZKi 7th Birthday Live Sweet POP Story
[Title: New Outfit Reveal & Major Announcement - AZKi 7th Birthday Live Sweet POP Story]